woodworkersjournal.com 2013-11-25

# Privacy Policy | Woodworkers Journal

| 

|   
---  
|    
| 

### Our website and Your Privacy

  * Our website 
  * What information is collected on this site?  

    * Information to Receive our Email Newsletters 
    * Information Necessary for Order Processing 
    * Your Phone and Fax Numbers
    * Non-Personal Information
  * Cookies 
  * How to Contact Us 

#### Our website

> This website is owned by Rockler Press, Inc. We currently do business as Woodworker's Journal. 
> 
> Our website is [woodworkersjournal.com  
>  ](http://woodworkersjournal.com/)
> 
> We have created this website to provide additional services to our customers and potential customers online. On our website you can: 

    * Shop our products securely online 
    * Subscribe to Woodworker's Journal magazine
    * Sign up for our free email newsletter, the Woodworker's Journal eZine 
    * Give us feedback and ask us questions about our magazine, products and website 
    * Read more about our magazine and products

#### Your Email Address

> If you supply us with your email address in an online form, we will send you a periodic email newsletter with links to articles on our website and other promotions on occasion. 
> 
> To be added to this list, please fill out our subscriber form found here. In each newsletter's email, you'll find a link to [our online profile management form](http://strongmail.woodworkersjournal.com/profile/primary/), where you'll be able to update your email preferences (including your email address) or remove your name and email address from this list. You can also send change- or removal-of-address requests to [contentcoordinator@woodworkersjournal.com](mailto:contentcoordinator@woodworkersjournal.com)
> 
> It has always been and will continue to be our policy not to share email addresses with third parties. 

#### Information for Order Processing

> If you place an order for a product on our website (such as a magazine subscription, back issue, CD/DVD, or downloadable plan), you will be asked to provide your name, mailing address, billing address, credit card number, email address and phone number in order to process, package and ship your order. 
> 
> We care very much about our customers' satisfaction and privacy. Our web servers are kept behind locked doors in a facility that is staffed and guarded 24 hours a day, 365 days a year. When it is necessary for you to supply sensitive information such as credit card numbers on our website, those communications travel from your browser all the way to our server protected by a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and are fully encrypted.
> 
> Occasionally, we make a portion of our list of subscribers to the Woodworker's Journal print magazine available to reputable organizations that may be of interest our customers. If you do not wish to have your information shared in this way, please send us a note saying so, along with your name and address, to the address below. 
> 
> Woodworker's Journal  
>  Customer Service  
>  4365 Willow Drive  
>  Medina, MN 55340 
> 
> You can also send this request and related information to [info@woodworkersjournal.com](mailto:info@woodworkersjournal.com) or call 1-800-765-4119

**Your Phone and Fax Numbers**

> If you supply us with your phone or fax number online, we may use them to contact you regarding an order you sent, or a question you asked. 
> 
> We do not share these numbers with other organizations. 

#### Cookies

> The paragraphs below outline some of the common practices used by a majority of publishing and ecommerce sites. A couple of terms you will need to know:
> 
> **Cookies** – These are small text files that are stored directly on your computer. They make it easier for the server to recognize your computer as you click from page to page (to keep track of your shopping cart as you browse our site, for example). The cookies do not actually contain any personal data.
> 
> **Pixel Tags** – these are very tiny images (smaller than the periods in this paragraph). They are there to inform our web server or e-mail server that you have opened an e-mail, for example, and to communicate other actions.
> 
> The Woodworker's Journal website, online services, interactive applications, e-mail messages, and advertisements may use "cookies" and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of our communications and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. 
> 
> Woodworker's Journal and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to "remember" how you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with our sites more convenient and personal. You may set your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. However, should you decide not to accept cookies from our sites, you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our sites.
> 
> As is true of most websites, our web servers gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Woodworker's Journal may use this information, as compiled in the aggregate and without personally identifying characteristics, in our marketing and advertising services.
> 
> Pixel tags enable us to send e-mail messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers. 

|    
  
---|---|---  
  
|  | 

---  
  
Sign up to receive the premier online woodworking newsletter. Get FREE plans, interviews, Q&As, techniques, and MORE! Best of all: IT'S FREE!!!

Click Here to learn more  |  View our Privacy Policy  
  
| Follow Us On  
---  
  
| 

|   
|   

ADVERTISEMENT

---  
| 

| 

| 

| 

| 

---|---|---|---|---  
  
[Subscribe](https://w1.buysub.com/servlet/OrdersGateway?cds_mag_code=WWJ&cds_page_id=101164) | [Change of Address](https://w1.buysub.com/servlet/CSGateway?cds_mag_code=WWJ) | [Gift Subscription](https://w1.buysub.com/servlet/GiftsGateway?cds_mag_code=WWJ&cds_page_id=62973)  |  Contact Us  |  [Advertising Info](http://ads.wwj.info/)  |  Privacy  |  [Follow @WoodworkersJrnl](http://twitter.com/WoodworkersJrnl)  
  
Copyright © 2013 Woodworker's Journal
